瑞秋  松饼加浓缩咖啡4块5
Okay, Rach, that's muffin and espresso, $4.50.
罗斯  双份拿铁2块75
Ross, double latte, $2.75.
钱德勒  咖啡和司康饼4块25
Chandler, coffee and a scone, $4.25.
菲比  花茶  1块25
And Pheebs, herbal tea, $1.25.
总共是...  12块75
All together that's $12.75.
不知80元电话费
This coming from the man
对半分是多少的人  居然能进步至此呢
who couldn't split our $80 phone bill in half.
你好
Hi.
我的松饼和拿铁多少钱
How much do I owe you for the muffin and the latte?
你的由乔伊·崔比安尼免费招待
That's on the house, courtesy of Joey Tribbiani.
真好  帮我谢谢他
Great. Well, tell him thanks.
既然乔伊人这么好
And since Joey seems like such a nice guy...
也许我们可以约个会
maybe we could go out on a date sometime?
他不太习惯女人这么主动
He's not used to women being so forward...
不过我问了他  他说好
but l could check with him. He says it's okay.
太好了  谢谢  再见
Great. Thanks. Bye- bye.
乔伊  为什么我们的不是免费
Hey Joey, how come our stuff isn't free?
等你穿窄裙也那么辣  我也给你免费
lt will be when you look like that in a tight skirt.
太爽了  最近约我的女人超级多
This is great! l'm getting more dates than ever.
慢着  你只给美女免费吗
Wait a minute. You're only giving free stuff to the pretty girls?
乔伊  那也太无耻了吧
Joey, that is so gross!
那你要不要来一块免费司康饼啊  宝贝
How about a scone on the house, baby?
我也是美女啊
l'm pretty.
-有人有口香糖吗  -我有
- Hey, does anyone have any gum? - l do.
拿一下
Here. Sorry.
找找啊
Oh, you know what?
也没有
No.
等一下
Wait a second.
-我包里的某处肯定有  -好吧
- l know it's in here. - You know what?
不用了  我不要了
l'm good. l'm good.
你怎么回来了  不是要上班吗
Why are you here? Shouldn't you be at work?
他们叫我回家
They sent me home..
说什么病了不能做菜
They said l can't work if l'm sick
-真可怜  -我才没病呢
- Sorry you're sick. - l'm not sick!
我从不生病
l don't get sick.
弱者跟娘炮才会生病感冒
Getting sick is for weaklings, it's for pansies.
宝贝  没有人觉得你娘娘腔
Honey, no one thinks that you're a pansy...
但我们觉得你需要面纸
...but we do think that you need a tissue.
我已经3年多没生过病了
l have not been sick in over three years.
我帮你拿几张面纸
l'm gonna grab you some tissue.
我不需要面纸  我很好...哪
l don't need a tissue. l'm fine-d.
好的后面还加个哪
When you put a D at the end of fine...
就不好哪
...you're not fine.
我很好...哪
l'm fine-d.
这句话发音不容易
You know, lt's a really hard word to say.
-谁啊  -你好
- Yes? - Hi.
瑞秋在吗  我是她的妹妹
ls Rachel here? l'm her sister.
天啊  吉尔
Oh, my God, Jill!
天啊  瑞秋
Oh, my God, Rachel!
天啊  介绍一下吧
Oh, my God, introduce us.
这位是钱德勒
This is Chandler.
你认识莫妮卡和罗斯
And you know Monica and Ross.
那是菲比  那是乔伊
And that's Phoebe. And that's Joey.
-你好吗  小妞  -不准乱来
- How you doing? - Don't!
宝贝  你怎么来了
Honey, what are you doing here?
这是哪个妹妹
Which sister is this?
被宠坏的那个  还是咬过她的
ls this the spoiled one or the one that bit her?
老爸断了我的财源
Daddy cut me off.
没关系  我知道了
Never mind, l got it.
你知道我怎么回他吗
You know what l said to him?
我说"我要请一个律师"
"I’m gonna hire a lawyer
"把你的钱都告过来"
and I’m gonna sue you and take all your money
"然后断了你的财源"
Then I’m gonna cut you off!"
那他怎么说
Wow. What did he say?
他说不帮我付律师费
That he wouldn't pay for my lawyer.
还叫我来跟他唯一自豪的女儿
Then he told me to learn the value of money...
学学金钱的价值
...from the one daughter he's actually proud of.
你们听到了吗  我爸以我为荣
Did you hear that? My dad's proud of me.
我爸以我为荣
My dad's proud of me.
-瑞秋  -好  抱歉
- Rach? - Oh, yeah. Sorry.
你做了什么让老爸气得断了你的财源
Honey, so what did you do that made Dad cut you off?
好吧  我买了一艘船
Okay, l bought a boat.
你买了一艘船啊
You bought a boat?
不是给自己买  是送人嘛
lt wasn't for me, it was for a friend.
天啊  我们应该跟另外一个女儿交朋友的
Boy, did we make friends with the wrong sister.
吉尔  亲爱的
Jill, honey.
这是你人生最好的一件事了
I think this is the best thing that could've happened to you.
反正你是也该独立自主了
I mean, you've needed to get out on your own any way.
我刚开始独立时也很怕
And you know what, when l did it, at first l was scared,
结果现在呢
but then look at me now.
我是唯一让老爸骄傲的女儿
l am the only daughter that Dad is proud of.
你现在要做的是
Okay, this is what you'll do.
找一份工作
You're gonna get a job.
找一间公寓
You're gonna get an apartment.
我会帮你  你可以跟我们住
and I'll help you, and you can stay with us.
对吧  菲比  她可以跟我们一起住
Right, Pheebs? She stay with us?
当然可以  没问题
Of course, yeah.
那真是太好了
Oh, that's so great!
好  我要发奋图强  自力更生
Okay, l'm really gonna do this.
真不知道该怎么谢谢你们
l don't know how to thank you guys.
我喜欢汽车
Oh, l like cars.
-您用餐完毕了吗  -是的
- You all finished? - Yes.
太好了
Great.
早上的小费出来了
Okay, here are the tips for this morning.
珍50块  我50块
Jen gets 50, 50 for me
乔伊欠8块
and Joey owes 8 dollars.
-什么  -因为你到处送吃的
- What? - For all the free food you gave away.
既然是白送的  为什么跟我要钱
lf it's free food, how come you're charging me for it?
本店只免费招待寿星
We don't give anything away unless it's one's birthday.
那模特儿比赛第三名呢
What if they came in third in a modeling contest?
不行
No.
抱歉
Sorry.
我今天累惨了
l just had the hardest day.
这些袋子好重
Some of these are so heavy.
吉尔  你怎么有钱
How did you pay for all these?
你爸不是把信用卡都收走了吗
l thought your dad took your credit card.
拜托  我15岁就会背卡号了
Oh please. l memorized those numbers when l was 15.
你们看我买的这些独立行头
But look at all the cool make- it- on- my- own stuff l got!
这是"请雇用我"毛衣
This is my "Please hire me" sweater.
这是  "你不想把房子租我吗"裤子
And these are my "Don't you want to rent me this apartment?" pants.
我不认为花老爸的钱买新衣
I don’t think charging new clothes to your dad
可以让你变得独立自主
qualifies as making it on your own.
大科学家就是这么死板
Oh, Mr. Scientist has to get all technical.
老实说  瑞秋看到这些应该会不高兴吧
Seriously, I don't think Rachel's not gonna think it's a good idea.
她什么时候当上女王了
So who made her queen of the world?
我倒是超想当女王的
l would love that job!
怎么样啊
What's going on?
吉尔
Jill!
你跑去逛街吗
Did you shop?
没有
No.
是他们
They did.
对  我们去逛街了
Yeah, we went shopping!
你们去逛街了
You went shopping?
然后还把东西秀给吉尔看
Then you came here and paraded it under Jill's nose...
你们不是知道她打算过节俭的生活吗
...when you know she's trying to quit.
你们真差劲
Well, you guys are just terrible.
-抱歉  吉尔  -对不起
- Sorry, Jill. - Sorry, Jill.
你们买了什么
So, what'd you get?
我买了...谢谢
Oh, well, all right. Thank you.
我买了这件  "我要工作"毛衣
l got this, you know, "l want a job" sweater.
还买了这条公寓裤
And then l got.... These are apartment pants.
公寓裤
Apartment pants?
对  你没听过吗
Yeah. You've never heard of them?
当然听过
Of course l've heard of them.
罗斯那你呢
Ross, what'd you get?
我买了这个...
l got this....
这个
This.
-帕什米纳的披肩  -对
- A pashmina? - Yeah!
我爱死它了
l love these babies.
是吗
Really?
罗斯  帕什米纳是什么
Ross, what's a pashmina?
一种小毯子
lt's a rug.
吉尔
Jill?
瑞秋  对不起...
l'm sorry, Rachel.
拜托  你觉得眼泪攻势会对我管用吗
Oh come on. You really think that's gonna work on me?
那是我发明的
l invented that.
也对
Right!
但我真的很抱歉
But l am sorry.
算了  一点点小错误是可以原谅的
All right. lt's okay. One little setback is okay.
-就是别再犯了  -好吗
- But don't let it happen again, alright? - Okay.
既然这是老爸付的钱
Now, since Daddy paid for all this stuff,
我应该全都没收
l should take it all away.
不过我没收披肩就好
But l'm just gonna take the pashmina.
还有那条裤子
And the pants.
算了  我还是全都没收好了
You know what, l'm just gonna take it all away,
这样你才能学到教训  知道吗
because that way, you'll learn the lesson, okay?
知道
Alrighty.
我有事要忙
Well, l'm gonna run a couple of errands
我们晚餐见
and l will see you at dinner.
都被她拿走了
She took all my stuff.
没错  除了这个蓝色小袋子
Yeah. Everything but the little blue one.
这一样最棒了
That's the best one!
天啊  谢谢你
Oh, my God. Thank you so much!
这个
Well, hey.
天啊  你好逊喔
Oh, my gosh, that was so lame.
帕什米纳怎么会是小毯子
Like a pashmina could be a rug.
那你呢   "对不起..."
Oh, yeah? How about you with the "l'm sorry "?
闭嘴  我哪有那么恶心
Shut up! l wasn't like that at all.
那我...那个公寓裤呢
What about what l said about the apartment pants?
够蠢吧
How dumb was l?
-你高中时有这么可爱吗  -别闹了
- Were you this cute in high school? - Oh, stop.
-你才别闹了  -你才别闹了
- No, you stop. - No, you stop.
你才别闹了
No, you stop.
好  我坐中间  你们都别闹了
Why don't l sit here and then you'll both stop it?
好的  你想做什么
Okay. So, what do you want to do?
我们来疯一下吧
Let's do something crazy.
我知道  我们来多休息多喝水
l know, let's rest and drink lots of fluids.
好  我休息
Okay, l'll rest.
不过如果我要上床
But you know, if l'm going to bed,
你也得跟我来
then you're coming with me.
这本来应该是很难拒绝的
See, that would be impossible to resist if you weren't all...
但是你鼻水流不停...
...drippy here.
你难道不想"品味"一下这曼妙身躯吗
Are you saying that you don't want to get with this?
我觉得刚才的话  就算你健康时也别说出口
l don't think you should say that even when you're healthy.
来嘛
Come on.
我不是针对你
Don't take this personally, ok?
我就是没办法跟病人上床
l just can't have sex with a sick person.
我也是啊  钱德勒
I'm with you,  Chandler.
我也不跟病人上床  那样好恶心
l can't have sex with a sick person either. Disgusting!
但是我没病
But l'm not sick!
让我证明给你看
Let me prove it to you.
我们俩都身强体壮
We are two healthy people
青春正"生"
in the prime of lime.
没错  我也是
See, that's the thing,
我也想维持青春正"盛"
l would like to stay in the "prime of lime."
怎么样啊
Hey. What's up?
有件事或许你应该知道
l think there's something you should maybe know.
最好不是公寓裤的事
Better not be about the apartment pants.
我刚刚向老板汇报了这个创意
l just pitched the idea to my boss at Ralph Lauren
她喜欢得不得了
and she loved it.
不是  你走后
No. lt's just, l was....
我和罗斯还有吉尔待在了一起
l was with Ross and Jill after you left...
我很确定他们之间有火花
...and l'm pretty sure l saw a little spark between them.
-什么  -应该是没什么吧
- What? - l mean, it's probably nothing.
我只是想提醒你  他们或许会有什么
But l wanted to warn you that there might be something there.
-罗斯跟吉尔吗  -对
- With Ross and Jill? - Yeah.
罗斯和我妹妹吗
With Ross and my sister?
对
Yeah.
我妹妹吉尔和我的前男友罗斯吗
With my sister Jill and my ex- boyfriend Ross?
对
Yeah.
-不可能的  -那好吧
- Oh, there is no way. - Okay, then.
我的天啊  我真不敢相信
Oh, my God! l cannot believe that!
我不反对罗斯交女朋友  但他泡我妹妹啊
I mean, l don't really like it when he dates anyone, but my sister?
这不是等于乱伦吗
lsn't that incest or something?
天啊  而且他们会上床
And they're gonna have sex.
要是他也娶了她呢
Oh, no! What if he marries her too?
太可怕了  真是太可怕了
This is just terrible. This is just terrible.
而我又不能阻止  罗斯又不是我的
And l can't stop it. l don't own Ross, you know?
而且吉尔有她的行动自由
And Jill should be able to do what she wants to do.
我的天啊  不敢相信罗斯居然要娶我妹
Oh, my God, l can't believe Ross is marrying my little sister.
这真是...
This is just...
这真是我这一生最悲惨的遭遇
This is the worst thing that could've ever happened to me.
不过公寓裤的事真是太好了
But great news about the apartment pants, huh?
总共3块85
That'll be $3.85.
什么意思
What do you mean?
昨天你还说我太美不该付钱
Yesterday you said l was too pretty to pay stuff.
我不能请客  因为经理说我...
lt's just, l can't, because my manager said that l- -
祝你生日快乐...
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐
-祝安妮生日快乐  -是艾米
- Happy birthday, dear Annie- - Amy!
艾米
Amy.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
真巧  今天也是我的生日
That's weird, today's my birthday too.
在这里不是
Not in here, it isn't.
抱歉迟到了  什么事
Sorry l'm late. What's up?
我只是想问你
You know, l just wanted to see if there were any leads
工作找得怎样
on the old job front.
没进展  但我经过三家折扣店都没进去
No. But l walked past three sales and didn't go in.
我很厉害吧
How strong am l?
太好了
That is great.
你知道谁不必找工作吗...  罗斯
You know who doesn't have to job hunt? Ross.
-他在大学教书  -是啊
- He works at the university. - Yeah?
所以你知道  你们聊过
So you know that? You guys talked about that?
你们很投缘  你们要约会吗
So you get along? So you're gonna go out?
我跟罗斯约会  不会啦
Me go out with Ross? No.
当然不会  你哪来的念头
God, no. What would make you think that?
菲比
Phoebe...
觉得你们俩可能会有点什么
...said she thought she saw something between you guys.
没有  他人是很好
l mean, he's nice.
你会想和他做朋友
He's the kind you're friends with,
但不会想和他交往
but not the kind you date.
他是你会交往的类型  事实也如此
He's the kind you date, because you did.
可我呢...
But me?
兴趣缺缺
Not so much.
没什么兴趣
Oh, not so much.
什么意思  罗斯有哪里不好吗
What do you mean? ls there something wrong with Ross?
没有  只不过
No, no, no. He's just....
我不知道
l don't know.
你了解的  他有点书生气
You know, he's just a little bookish.
你觉得他是书呆吗
Are you saying he's a geek?
你也有同感吗
You think so too?
不  罗斯才不是书呆
No. Ross is not a geek.
好  他不是我喜欢的型可以了吧
Fine. Then let's just say he's not my type.
帅哥不是你的型吗
Handsome is not your type?
聪明  好心  吻功一流
Smart, kind, good kisser.
这些都不是你的择偶条件吗
What, those things aren't on your list?
罗斯人很好  能跟他在一起是你的福气
Ross is great. You'd be lucky to be with him.
好  既然你这么在意  我就约他吧
Okay, if it means that much, then l'll ask him out.
不不不  我不是那个意思
Oh, no. That's not what l meant.
你知道吗   瑞秋  你说得对
You know what? Rachel, you're right.
他对我确实很好
You know he has been really nice to me.
但他不是你的型
Yeah, but he's not your type.
或许这是好事
But maybe that's good thing.
我正在尝试不一样的人生
l'm doing all these different things.
或许也应该跟个书呆约会看看
Maybe l should just try dating a geek too.
但也别一下子尝试太多新东西啊
Yeah, but you don't want to try too much too fast.
我是说  你记得那个一下子
You know what I mean, you do remember what happened to the little girl
做太多尝试的小女孩吧
who tried too much too fast, don't you?
什么
What?
她死了  吉尔
She died, Jill.
钱德勒
Chandler!
什么事  亲爱的
What is it, honey?
你想喝茶  还是喝汤
You need some tea? Some soup?
呼叫巨根医生
Calling Dr. Big.
巨根医生请上床
Dr. Big to the bed.
天啊  宝贝  我以为你睡了
Jeez, honey, l thought you were asleep.
你就在外面
How could l be asleep
我怎么睡得着
knowing that you were in the next room?
我倒是睡着了
l was asleep.
不不不  宝贝
Oh, no, no, honey.
你知道怎样才性感  多穿几层
You know what's sexy? Layers.
多穿几层才性感
Layers are sexy.
被子才性感
And blankets are sexy.
热水瓶更性感
And hot-water bottles are sexy.
快点上床啦
Come on, get into bed.
我想证明我没生病
l want to prove l'm not sick.
我想让你跟我一样舒服
l want to make you feel as good as l feel.
我拜托你休息
Would you please get some rest?
我没事哪
l'm fine.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
-钱你出  -不  今天是她的生日
- You're paying for that. - No, it's her birthday.
你今天已经对二十个女人唱生日快乐歌了
You've sung ''Happy Birthday'' to 20 women today.
你失去送生日松饼的权限了
You are no longer authorized to distribute birthday muffins.
我靠
Damn it!
瑞秋
Rachel.
是你叫你妹妹约我吗
Did you tell your sister to ask me out?
-对...  -哇  真是哇
- Well, yeah. - Oh, wow! l mean, wow.
我觉得她很可爱  但
l think she's cute, but...
我从来没想过要跟她约会
...l never would've thought of going out with her.
从没有过
Never!
真的  不过既然你说行
Really? But after you said it's okay,
我心想  "有何不可"
l figured, "Why not"
所以也不算从来没想过
Oh, so not really ''never.''
不得不说  你真的比我大方多了
l have to say you are a much bigger person than l am.
毕竟我们一起经历了那么多
l mean, after all we've been through.
我真希望我有兄弟可以做交换
l wish l had a brother to reciprocate.
如果你想跟莫妮卡交往  我绝对祝福
lf you ever date Monica, you have my blessing.
我也祝福
And mine.
钱德勒
Chandler?
我觉得我病了
l think l'm sick.
是吗
Really?
青春不"剩"了
Struck down in the "pribe of libe."
好啦  我承认
Okay, fine, l admit it.
我很不舒服
l feel terrible.
帮我在胸口抹药膏
Will you please rub this on my chest?
不行  不行
No, no, no.
你别想骗我上钩
You are not getting me this way.
我真的需要你帮我...  不行
- Come on, l really need your help here. - No, no no no no.
-好  那我就自己抹  -好
- Fine, l'll rub it on myself. - Okay.
你这是在抹药膏吗
So you're just kind of rubbing it on yourself?
-怎样  -真不错
- Yeah. - lt's nice.
不会吧  这样你会兴奋吗
Are you kidding me? ls this turning you on?
对
Yes.
真是太扯了  是抹的动作还是味道
I can't believe it. ls it the rubbing or the smell?
都很赞很兴奋
lt's all very, very good.
想不想...
So you want to go...
嘿咻一下
...mix it up?
现在不行  我病了
Not now, l'm sick.
少来了  别装了
Oh, come on, you big faker!
你之前不是说不跟病人上床吗
What happened to your rule about never sleeping with sick people?
那是在那令人酥麻的动作之前
Well, that was before all the vaporizing action.
-好吧  如果你真的想做的话  -好
- Okay, if you really want to have sex. - Okay.
百试百灵啊
Worked like a charm.
你来这里干什么
Wh-what are you doing here?
我跟罗斯约会就在这里
This is where Ross and l are meeting for our date.
我的打扮如何
So, what do you think?
我不喜欢
l don't like it.
-是吗  -有点放荡
- Really? - lt's kind of slutty.
这是你的衣服
lt's yours.
我就是个荡妇
Yeah, well, l'm a slut.
我也是
Me too.
吉尔
Hi, Jill.
瑞秋
- Rachel. - Rachel.
你不在家  你在这里
You're not at home, you're right here.
我知道
Yeah, l know.
你一定以为会很怪
And l bet you thought it would be weird.
其实不会嘛
But it's not.
好
Okay.
这个...
So, well, l'll....
我午夜之前会送她回家
l'll have her home by midnight.
你为什么还没回家
Why aren't you home yet?
外面有人吗
ls someone there?
有  是我  抱歉
Oh, yeah, it's me. Sorry.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
我只是在看窗外...
l'm just looking out your window
的风景
at the view.
你们在干什么
What are you guys doing?
我们身上某些部位沾到了药膏
We got some vapor rub in some places.
他把她带回家了
He brought her back to his apartment.
谁
Who?
那是妹妹吗
Is that your sister?
她果然是个荡妇
Ugh, she is a slut!
天啊  罗斯在跟你妹约会
Oh my god! Ross is on a date with your sister.
多奇怪啊
How weird is that?
天啊  看  他在脱她的衣服
Oh, my God, he's taking off her clothes!
他只是在帮她脱外套
He's taking off her coat.
真是太糟糕了
Oh, this is just terrible.
不会啦  才第一次约会
Oh, no, it's not. lt's a first date.
我肯定他们一定不...
l'm sure that nothing is gonna....
不会不"搞"
He's gonna get some.
搞到心烦
Of the glare...
我是说他家外的街灯太亮  搞到人心烦
...from the streetlight out of his apartment.
所以他得把窗帘拉上
You know, so he's closed the drapes there...
才能好好跟你妹妹
...so he can have a nice, pleasant...
坐在客厅聊聊天
...conversation with your little sister.
好啦  我要去睡了
Well, l'm off to bed.